<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-12-26T00:41:08+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">3SB01_6210110013</title><subtitle>เว็บไซต์นี้เป็นส่วนหนึงของงานในวิชา 240-302  Advanced Computer Engineering Lab II </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Stand by Me Doraemon 2 (2020)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/15/Stand-by-Me-Doraemon-2-(2020).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stand by Me Doraemon 2 (2020)" /><published>2021-12-15T01:28:34+07:00</published><updated>2021-12-15T01:28:34+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/15/Stand%20by%20Me%20Doraemon%202%20(2020)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/15/Stand-by-Me-Doraemon-2-(2020).html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;storyline&quot;&gt;Storyline&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One day Nobita Nobi found a old stuffed bear which his grandmother gave it to him. Nobita decided to go back in time to meet his grandmother. Grandma accepts Nobita’s belief that he is a young child who has suddenly arrived. Nobita’ s grandmother said “I want to see your bride once.” And from this one sentence of grandma Doraemon and Nobita’s big blasphemy begins. Nobita and Doraemon were trying to show their grandmother a marriage ceremony, but Adult Nobita escaped on the day of his marriage ceremony. Adult Gian and Suneo looking for Nobita. Shizuka who keeps waiting with confidence. Nobita and Doraemon take the time to fulfill the wishes of grandma, to meet the wishes of her family, friends and Shizuka Minamoto, who she likes very much.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://shorturl.asia/cnrvg?raw=true&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;official-trailer&quot;&gt;Official Trailer&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5bDCZMdKa_4&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt13428402/&quot;&gt;credit!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Storyline One day Nobita Nobi found a old stuffed bear which his grandmother gave it to him. Nobita decided to go back in time to meet his grandmother. Grandma accepts Nobita’s belief that he is a young child who has suddenly arrived. Nobita’ s grandmother said “I want to see your bride once.” And from this one sentence of grandma Doraemon and Nobita’s big blasphemy begins. Nobita and Doraemon were trying to show their grandmother a marriage ceremony, but Adult Nobita escaped on the day of his marriage ceremony. Adult Gian and Suneo looking for Nobita. Shizuka who keeps waiting with confidence. Nobita and Doraemon take the time to fulfill the wishes of grandma, to meet the wishes of her family, friends and Shizuka Minamoto, who she likes very much.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stand by Me Doraemon (2014)</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/14/Stand-by-Me-Doraemon-(2014).html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stand by Me Doraemon (2014)" /><published>2021-12-14T01:28:34+07:00</published><updated>2021-12-14T01:28:34+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/14/Stand%20by%20Me%20Doraemon%20(2014)</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/14/Stand-by-Me-Doraemon-(2014).html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;storyline&quot;&gt;Storyline&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What will happen to Nobita’s life after Doraemon leaves?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In the suburbs of Tokyo some time ago, there lived a clumsy boy about 10 years old. There appeared in front of him named Sewashi, Nobita’s descendant of four generations later from the 22nd century, and Doraemon, a 22nd century cat-type caretaker robot who helps people with its secret gadgets. Sewashi claims that his family is suffering from the debts Nobita made even to his generation, so in order to change this disastrous future, he brought along Doraemon as Nobita’s caretaker to bring happiness to his future, although Doraemon is not happy about this. And so Sewashi installed an accomplishment program into Doraemon forcing him to take care of Nobita. Unless he makes Nobita happy, Doraemon can no longer go back to the 22nd century. This is how the life of Doraemon and Nobita begins. Will Doraemon succeed this mission and return to the 22nd century?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;In Tokyo a young boy named Nobita Noby who has a hard time with his life but his life is changed when a robot cat from the 22nd century named doraemon apears out of his drawer with his decedent of 4 generations Sewashi Sony he tells Noby his family is becoming poor but Doraemon doesn’t care so so by installs a program that forces Doraemon to take care of Noby and try making him happy but Noby has trouble with his home, friends and his crush on shizuka but Doraemon can’t go back to the 22nd century until he make Noby happy, this is the story of Doraemon and Noby begins but will Doraemon stay with Noby and help him forever?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://shorturl.asia/E7D4F?raw=true&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;official-trailer&quot;&gt;Official Trailer&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oiK8ObSYRb8&quot;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt3331846/&quot;&gt;credit!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">Storyline What will happen to Nobita’s life after Doraemon leaves?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/13/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2021-12-13T01:28:34+07:00</published><updated>2021-12-13T01:28:34+07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/13/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/12/13/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR&lt;/code&gt; is a four-digit number, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MONTH&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DAY&lt;/code&gt; are both two-digit numbers, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&apos;Tom&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &apos;Hi, Tom&apos; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry></feed>